[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "What do you think -- if your brain path for this kind of thing, what can we confidently predict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "CD", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "Would that have been a good thing for the president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "LITZER: It probably would have been but I think they've assumed from day one that Mitt Romney is going to be the Republican presidential nominee.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ron Paul"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "If either of those candidates pulled out, where would their votes go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Ron Paul is not going anywhere, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Arizona"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "So how are you feeling overall about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "Well, I'm feeling like it was a big win in Arizona and we're just really pleased that the people rallied around the man that we believe can move forward and beat President Obama.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "What would you be advising him to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Well, I think that the bottom line is that he's -- you know, he's leading in the race.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Is that what you want to see from Mitt Romney when the battle royale starts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "Now, Piers, you don't know what I was saying.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Just to be serious, I mean if Mitt Romney does win and is the nominee and he gets to take on Barack Obama, should he be making some kind of advantage of the apparent thin-skinned that you've identified?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VB", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Oh, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "So I mean he's got it in him, isn't he, to really stick the knife in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "Well, you know, I will be honest with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney", "Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "So why did you switch?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "Well, you know, I originally, I think, bought into the conventional wisdom that Governor Romney was the strongest candidate against Barack Obama.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Michigan"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "I mean given that Mitt Romney has won both in Arizona and Michigan tonight, I mean, do you feel a bit that guy that put everything on red in Vegas and then came out black?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, I don't think Governor Romney can be very happy with his performance in Michigan.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "LOCATION": ["Arizona", "Michigan", "Vegas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "What are you going to do about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "There's a great deal of enthusiasm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Santorum"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Did President Kennedy's speech about the separation of church and state make you want to throw up and do you think it's snobbish for the president of the United States to want people to go to college?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Well, I think -- I think Senator Santorum has explained exactly what he meant.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kennedy"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", ",", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Are you any clearer about what the motive may have been for this senseless killing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "It's not clear at all what the motive is, what the motive was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Is there a family rift about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "No, not at all, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ohio", "Michigan"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", ":", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "What is your sense about the way it's going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Well, I think, I think Ohio is going to be a lot like we saw with Michigan over the course of the last week and I would suggest to your viewers that -- that they just throw out any poll they have seen so far.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Do those things really matter on the ground in somewhere like Michigan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "They absolutely do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Michigan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "How damaging is a prolonged race or could it be like the Democrat race four years ago where actually it ends up being quite helpful?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBG", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Well, I think it -- I think it could be helpful but I'll tell you what.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Have you changed your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "I have not changed my mind, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Have you changed your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "Well, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBG", "JJ", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "So I mean, are you in possession of information that I'm not in possession of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, look, if you think about what being bankrupt is, it isn't going out of business.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "I mean, it's not a winning proposition for any candidate in a presidential election, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Yes, but it's not -- it's not a success.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Well -- yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "If I could just jump in and...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "You know, has he got a way back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "The professor always has a way back in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "VB", "CD", "CC", "CD", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Would it be enough, even if he wins in Georgia?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Oh, Newt'll probably think it's enough, but he should probably try and win one or two more on that same day.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Georgia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["20 percent"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "CD", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Is it a real possibility?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Well, it -- now at RealClearPolitics, it's up to 20 percent, when it was down in single digits before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WP", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "I mean, is there anybody realistically who's going to stick their neck out now and take on Barack Obama in an election that many think they couldn't win?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "NN", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RP", "RB", "CC", "VB", "RP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "You know, it's really hard to see who that person would be.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Who's at the top of the ticket?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Sarah...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 552, "question": "What media scrutiny?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 553, "answer": "Well, there was enough...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ":"], "qSentId": 563, "question": "You also don't chose someone at the last minute as your potential nominee who hasn't been thoroughly vetted for a while by the media, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 564, "answer": "One of the other...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Who?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2008"], "PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Amy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Oh, boy, you know, I had predicted Hillary Clinton in 2008, so I'm not sure my prediction is worth much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Carol?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "I'm voting for you, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "Why did you and Mitt Romney part company just after the Florida debate, where by common consent, you'd got him back on track?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WRB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "Well, I'm not going to, you know, comment on the details of what happened with the Romney campaign, but I was very honored to be able to work with him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "LOCATION": ["Florida"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Why is he still struggling to really cement this front-runner position, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "Well, I mean, I think, you know, this race has been all about momentum, and there's been a lag between some of the contests.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "I mean, knowing Mitt Romney as you do, what is it that he's struggling to get out there about his character, his personality, that perhaps he isn't selling well enough yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Well, I mean, I think it's the personal side.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}]